http://www.asifcu.org/privacy/

OnPath Credit UnionBreadcrumb page navigationHomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyWhat does OnPath Financial Federal Credit Union do with your personal information? What does OnPath Federal Credit Union do with your personal information? Why?Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.What?The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security number and incomeAccount balances and transaction historyCredit history and payment historyWhen you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.How?All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons OnPath Financial Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.Reasons we can share your personal informationReasons we can share your personal informationDoes OnPath Federal Credit Union share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes - such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausYesNoFor our marketing purposes - to offer our products and services to youYesNoFor joint marketing with other financial companiesYesNoFor our affiliates' everyday business purposes— information about your transactions and experiencesNoWe don’t shareFor our affiliates' everyday business purposes— information about your creditworthinessNoWe don’t shareFor our affiliates to market to youNoWe don’t shareFor nonaffiliates to market to youNoWe don’t shareWho We AreWho We AreWho is providing this notice?OnPath Federal Credit UnionWhat We DoWhat We DoHow does OnPath Federal Credit Union protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.How does OnPath Federal Credit Union collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when youopen an account or provide account informationapply for a loan or use your credit or debit cardgive us your contact informationWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.Why can't I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit onlysharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes— information about your creditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for nonaffiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.DefinitionsTermDefinititionAffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.OnPath Federal Credit Union does not share with our affiliates.NonaffiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. OnPath Federal Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.Joint marketing A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.Our joint marketing partners include financial and insurance companies.Questions? Call 504.733.7274 or toll free 800.749.6193.Download Our Privacy Notice
